https://www.english.ox.ac.uk/privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy Statement
This website runs on Oxford Mosaic, the University of Oxford’s web platform. The Oxford Mosaic Privacy Statement explains what types of personal information will generally be gathered when you visit sites created using the platform. Where this specific site differs, or collects additional information, further details are given below.
1. How we use cookies
Our web pages use "cookies". A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we place on your computer or mobile device if you agree. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allow us to improve our website.
Cookies may be set either by the this website ("first party cookies"), or by a third party website ("third party cookies"). The tables below identify the cookies we use and explain the purposes for which they are used.
However, we continue to collect information about third-party cookies and the tables below are based on the work completed to date. Accordingly, we may update the information contained in this section from time to time.
Drupal
This website is run on the Drupal content management system (CMS). Drupal sets some cookies in order to improve the user experience and assist in the delivery of the site (e.g. to test whether a user has JavaScript enabled.) The following cookies are set by Drupal on this site:
Cookie ID
Purpose
Contains or Links to personal data
Data
Type
Lifespan
SESS[random string]
Determines whether or not a user is logged in so that Drupal can optimise performance for non-logged in users
no
unique string
Session
23 days
has_js
Determines whether or not JavaScript is enabled so that Drupal can more efficiently perform operations to enhance the user experience
no
boolean
Session
End of session
cookie-agreed-en
Records whether or not the cookies notification pop-up has been acknowledged by a user
no
numerical
Persistent
100 days
Google Analytics
This site uses Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use our site. Google Analytics uses cookies to record information about usage. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. For further information on how Google Analytics handles user data please see the Google Analytics privacy policy. The table below shows details of the cookies that Google analytics uses:
Cookie ID
Purpose
Contains or Links to personal data
Data
Type
Lifespan
__utma
Tracking for statistics
no
Visitor ID (Anonymous)
Persistent
30
__utmb
Tracking for statistics
no
Visitor ID (Anonymous)
Persistent
30 mins
__utmc
Tracking for statistics
no
Visitor ID (Anonymous)
Session
End of Session
__utmz
Tracking for statistics
no
Visitor ID (Anonymous)
Persistent
6 months
2. Further information
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
3. Changes to our Cookie Statement
Any changes we may make to our Cookie Statement in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you.
powered by
oxford mosaic
List of site pages
